<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>St. Helena Ministries - Daily Rosary</title>
    <description>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.
	</description>
    <link>https://sthelenaministries.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 St Helena Ministries</copyright>
    
    <atom:link href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:author>St Helena Ministries</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>St Helena Ministries</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>divineoffice@sthelenaministries.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/rosary-artwork.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
      <itunes:category text="Christianity" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
   
  <item><title>TEST PUBLISH STEP 1110</title><description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather in prayer to meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, reflecting on the early life of our Lord and the humble faith of the Holy Family. Through this sacred devotion, listeners are invited to enter more deeply into the mystery of God’s love revealed in the Incarnation, as recounted in the Gospels of Matthew and Luke. The gentle rhythm of the Rosary offers a moment of calm and spiritual nourishment amid the busyness of daily life.

If this prayerful time has touched your heart, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue sharing the beauty of the Rosary with others. Your generosity sustains our mission and allows us to offer these prayers freely.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which guides listeners through the Liturgy of the Hours with reverence and clarity.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace as you walk with Mary and the saints in faith.</description><enclosure url="https://archive.org/details/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" /><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-29-joyful-mysteries</guid></item></channel>
</rss>