<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>St. Helena Daily Rosary</title>
    <description>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.
	</description>
    <link>https://sthelenaministries.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 St Helena Ministries</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:author>St Helena Ministries</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>St Helena Ministries</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>divineoffice@sthelenaministries.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/rosary-artwork.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
      <itunes:category text="Christianity" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-02 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. As we reflect on these sacred moments, the rosary offers a serene space for contemplation and spiritual renewal. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping to sustain our mission of daily prayer and faith formation. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the timeless prayers of the Church throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred devotions. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-02-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-02-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-01 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we gather in quiet prayer to meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting the light of Christ’s public ministry to illuminate our hearts. As we reflect on these sacred moments, drawn from the Gospel accounts, we are gently led to deepen our faith and trust in God’s presence. This prayerful time offers a peaceful space to unite our intentions with those of the Church, fostering spiritual growth through contemplative repetition and Scripture references from the Gospels.

If this ministry nourishes your prayer life, please consider supporting us so we can continue to provide daily prayer resources. Your generosity helps sustain this humble offering of faith and devotion.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers throughout the liturgical hours are prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-01-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-01-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-12-31 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Glorious Mysteries, reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the gift of the Holy Spirit, among other profound moments in the life of Christ and Our Lady. This prayer invites a peaceful meditation on the triumph of grace and the hope found in God’s promises, drawing from the scriptural accounts in the Gospels and the Acts of the Apostles. Join us in this calm and reverent time of prayer as we unite our hearts with the Church’s daily devotion.

If this ministry helps nourish your prayer life, please consider supporting our work. Your generosity enables us to continue providing these daily prayers freely to all who seek to deepen their faith.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer rhythm further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, offering the Church’s official prayers throughout the day.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual renewal.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-31-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-31-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2029-12-30 Daily Rosary - Sorrowful Mysteries</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. Through each mystery, we reflect on the profound love and mercy revealed in these moments of Christ’s suffering, drawing strength and grace from this sacred devotion. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us to continue offering these daily prayers freely to all who seek spiritual nourishment. For those wishing to enrich their prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which guides listeners through the Church’s daily liturgical prayers. Thank you for joining us in this peaceful time of contemplation and prayer. May God’s peace be with you always.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-30-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2029-12-30-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-12-29 Daily Rosary - Joyful Mysteries</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the loving heart of Our Blessed Mother. As we reflect on these sacred events, drawn from the Gospels, we seek to grow in faith and devotion through contemplative prayer. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping to sustain these daily moments of spiritual nourishment and community prayer. For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s traditional prayers throughout the day. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace as you journey with us in faith.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-29-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-29-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>