<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>St. Helena Daily Rosary</title>
    <description>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.
	</description>
    <link>https://sthelenaministries.com</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2024 St Helena Ministries</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/podcast.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type>
    <itunes:author>St Helena Ministries</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Pray the Holy Rosary each day with St. Helena Ministries through a calm, reverent daily Rosary podcast rooted in traditional Catholic prayer. Each episode follows the mysteries of the Rosary for the day of the week, inviting you to meditate on the life of Christ through the heart of His Blessed Mother.
St. Helena Daily Rosary is designed as a quiet companion for daily Catholic devotion — at home, during your commute, or in moments of reflection. With a faithful structure and gentle pace, this podcast supports consistent prayer and meditation on the mysteries of the Holy Rosary.
For those who also pray the Liturgy of the Hours, we invite you to listen to our companion podcast, Daily Prayer with the Divine Office, offering the Office of Readings, Morning, Evening, and Night Prayer.
To support this ministry and help us continue providing daily Catholic prayer resources, visit <a href="sthelenaministries.com/support">sthelenaministries.com</a>.</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>St Helena Ministries</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>divineoffice@sthelenaministries.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://sthelenaministries.github.io/podcast-daily-rosary/rosary-artwork.png" />
    <itunes:category text="Religion &amp; Spirituality">
      <itunes:category text="Christianity" />
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-23 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. Each mystery is thoughtfully reflected upon, allowing space for quiet contemplation and spiritual renewal rooted in the Gospel accounts found in the early chapters of Matthew and Luke. This daily prayer offers a serene moment to unite your intentions with the Church’s tradition of honoring these joyful moments of the Incarnation and early life of Jesus.

If this ministry has been a source of grace for you, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to provide these prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our mission of prayer and formation.

For those wishing to deepen their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which guides listeners through the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours with reverence and clarity.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-23-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-23-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-22 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the gift of the Holy Spirit, among others, as presented in the Gospel and the Acts of the Apostles. Each mystery is gently guided to foster a deeper connection with Christ’s triumph and the hope of eternal life. We encourage you to enter into this time of peaceful contemplation and spiritual renewal.

If you find this prayerful offering meaningful, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue sharing the beauty of Catholic prayer daily. Your generosity sustains our mission and outreach.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s liturgical hours are prayed with reverence and devotion.

May this time of prayer bring you calm and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-22-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-22-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-21 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter into the joyful moments of Our Lord’s early life with Mary and Joseph. Through this sacred prayer, we reflect on the Annunciation, the Visitation, the Nativity, the Presentation in the Temple, and the Finding of Jesus in the Temple, drawing closer to the mysteries of faith as revealed in the Gospel of Luke. Join us in this calm and reverent recitation, allowing the Rosary to deepen your daily communion with Christ and His Blessed Mother.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work to help us continue offering these prayers freely. Your generosity enables us to reach more souls seeking peace and grace.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed throughout the day.

May this time of prayer bring you quiet consolation and spiritual renewal.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-21-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-21-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-20 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the Passion of our Lord Jesus Christ. As we reflect on these sacred moments, drawn from the Gospels, we unite our hearts with Mary’s sorrow and Christ’s loving sacrifice. This daily prayer offers a serene space to grow in faith and trust through contemplative prayer. If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting us so we can continue to provide these spiritual resources freely. We also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s daily prayers are prayed in the rhythm of the liturgical hours, enriching your journey in the Word of God. Visit our website to learn more. May this time of prayer bring you peace and closeness to Christ’s heart.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-20-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-20-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-19 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting listeners to enter more deeply into the public ministry of Jesus Christ. Each mystery is presented with reverence and calm reflection, guiding the faithful through moments of grace found in the Gospel accounts of the Baptism in the Jordan, the Wedding at Cana, the Proclamation of the Kingdom, the Transfiguration, and the Institution of the Eucharist. This prayerful journey encourages a quiet encounter with the Lord, fostering spiritual growth and contemplation rooted in Scripture, particularly from the Gospels.

We humbly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide daily prayer resources that nourish the soul and strengthen faith. Your generosity sustains our mission and enables us to share these sacred prayers with a wider community.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we also recommend the Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official prayer of the hours, complementing the Rosary with the rhythm of the liturgical day.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a deeper awareness of God’s presence in your life.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-19-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-19-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-18 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we pray the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to meditate on the Resurrection, Ascension, Descent of the Holy Spirit, the Assumption, and the Coronation of Mary. Through these sacred moments, we enter into a peaceful reflection on the triumph of Christ and the hope of eternal life, guided by Scripture references from the Gospels and Acts. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to offer daily prayer resources that nourish the soul and deepen faith. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official prayer at morning, midday, evening, and night. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred rhythms. May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual refreshment.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-18-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-18-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-17 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we pray the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter deeply into the passion of Christ through contemplative prayer. Each mystery is meditated upon with reverence and quiet reflection, drawing from the Gospel accounts in the books of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. This prayerful time offers a peaceful space to unite your intentions with the sufferings of Our Lord.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work to help us continue providing daily prayers and reflections. Your generosity enables us to share these moments of grace with a wider community.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day in union with the universal Church.

May this time of prayer bring you closer to the heart of Christ and deepen your trust in His mercy.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-17-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-17-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-16 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, join us in prayer as we meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, reflecting on the early life of Our Lord and the profound moments of grace revealed through the Annunciation, Visitation, Nativity, Presentation, and Finding in the Temple. This peaceful time of prayer invites you to enter more deeply into the Gospel, fostering a spirit of quiet contemplation and devotion. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide daily prayers and reflections that nourish the soul. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and care. Visit our website to learn more or to offer your support. May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-16-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-16-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-15 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the coming of the Holy Spirit, as well as the Assumption and Coronation of Mary. Each mystery is presented with reverence, guiding you through a peaceful and contemplative prayer experience rooted in Scripture from the Gospels and Acts. We encourage you to enter into this sacred time of prayer with calm and devotion.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work so we can continue to provide daily prayers and reflections. Your generosity helps sustain this humble mission.

For those seeking to deepen their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with the same care and reverence.

May this time of prayer bring you closer to the peace and grace of our Lord.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-15-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-15-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-14 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this February 14, 2026 episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ through the eyes of His Blessed Mother. Each decade offers a moment to reflect on the Annunciation, Visitation, Nativity, Presentation, and Finding in the Temple, drawing from the Gospel accounts in Luke and Matthew. This sacred time of prayer nurtures a spirit of quiet contemplation and devotion.

If you find spiritual nourishment in these daily prayers, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue offering these moments of grace freely. Your generosity sustains our mission to bring the Rosary and other devotions to hearts around the world.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers unfold throughout the day, deepening your connection to the liturgical rhythm.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer union with Our Lord and His Blessed Mother.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-14-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-14-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-13 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we pray the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting listeners to meditate on the profound moments of Christ’s Passion. Through each mystery, we reflect on the depth of Our Lord’s love and sacrifice, fostering a spirit of quiet contemplation and prayerful union. This prayerful journey offers a moment of peace amid daily life, drawing us closer to the heart of the Gospel as revealed in the Scriptures.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work to continue bringing these prayers to the faithful. Your generosity helps sustain this humble offering of prayer and reflection.

For those seeking to deepen their daily prayer life, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-13-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-13-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-12 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the public ministry of Our Lord Jesus Christ. As we contemplate these sacred moments, drawn from the Gospels, we seek to grow in faith and devotion through the gentle rhythm of the Rosary. This prayerful reflection offers a peaceful space to unite your heart with the Church’s daily prayer.

If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting our work so that we may continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our mission of spreading the beauty of Catholic prayer.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and deepen your communion with Christ and His Mother.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-12-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-12-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-11 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to meditate on the Resurrection, Ascension, Descent of the Holy Spirit, the Assumption of Mary, and the Coronation of Our Lady. Through these sacred reflections, we seek to deepen our communion with Christ and His Mother, following the rhythm of daily Catholic prayer. The scriptural foundations for these mysteries can be found in the Gospels and Acts. We encourage you to join us in this peaceful devotion, fostering a spirit of reverence and trust in God’s providence. If this ministry enriches your prayer life, please consider supporting our work to help us continue offering these prayers freely. For those who desire to extend their daily prayer, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which complements the Rosary by praying the Liturgy of the Hours throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to support this ministry. May this time of prayer bring you grace and serenity.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-11-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-11-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-10 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter deeply into the passion of our Lord Jesus Christ. Through each mystery, we reflect on His suffering and love, drawing strength and grace from this sacred devotion. The prayers are offered with reverence, guiding you gently through this time of contemplation and union with Christ’s redemptive sacrifice, as found in the Gospels, particularly in the accounts of His passion.

If this ministry enriches your prayer life, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to provide these daily moments of spiritual nourishment. Your generosity helps sustain our mission to bring the beauty of Catholic prayer to all who seek it.

For those wishing to deepen their daily prayer rhythm, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day, fostering a continuous encounter with God.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with our Lord.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-10-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-10-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-09 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. Through this sacred devotion, we reflect on the joyful events that reveal God’s loving plan, drawing from the Gospel accounts found in the early chapters of the Gospels. Join us as we unite our hearts in this ancient prayer, seeking grace and peace in the quiet moments of contemplation.

If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting our work to help us continue offering these daily prayers freely to all. Your generosity sustains our mission and allows us to share the beauty of Catholic prayer with a wider community.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers throughout the day are prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you calm and a deeper sense of God’s presence in your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-09-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-09-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-08 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting listeners to enter more deeply into the resurrection and triumph of our Lord as revealed in the Gospel and the Acts of the Apostles. Each decade is prayed with reverence and calm, fostering a spirit of contemplation and devotion rooted in Scripture from the New Testament. We encourage you to join us in this sacred prayer, allowing the mysteries to inspire hope and faith in your daily life. If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work to help us continue offering these prayers freely. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer rhythm further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s liturgical prayers are prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to support this ministry. May this time of prayer bring you peace and draw you closer to Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-08-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-08-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-07 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we pray the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to meditate on the joyful events in the life of Our Lord and Our Lady. Through this sacred prayer, we reflect on moments such as the Annunciation and the Nativity, drawing closer to the heart of the Gospel as revealed in the Scriptures. Join us in this peaceful time of prayer and contemplation, fostering a deeper connection with God’s love and grace.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to offer these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our mission of prayer and formation.

For those wishing to expand their daily prayer life, we also invite you to listen to our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official daily prayers, enriching your journey in faith throughout the day.

May this time of prayer bring you quiet peace and renewed hope.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-07-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-07-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-06 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of our Lord Jesus Christ. Through these sacred reflections, we accompany Him in moments of profound suffering, drawing strength and grace from His example. Each mystery is prayed with reverence, fostering a peaceful space for contemplation and spiritual renewal. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to offer these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. For those desiring to enrich their daily prayer life further, we encourage you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s liturgical prayers are prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred rhythms. May this time of prayer bring you quiet peace and deepen your communion with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-06-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-06-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-05 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting you to reflect on the public ministry of Jesus Christ as revealed in the Gospels of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. Through these mysteries, we contemplate the Baptism in the Jordan, the Wedding at Cana, the Proclamation of the Kingdom, the Transfiguration, and the Institution of the Eucharist, deepening our union with Christ in a spirit of reverence and peace. We warmly encourage you to support this ministry, helping to sustain these daily moments of prayer and spiritual nourishment. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider also listening to our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours in a calm and accessible format. Visit our website to learn more or to offer your support. May this time of prayer bring you closer to the heart of Christ and fill your day with grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-05-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-05-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-04 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the coming of the Holy Spirit, among other sacred events. This daily prayer offers a moment of calm and reverence, drawing us closer to the heart of Christ through the intercession of Our Lady. As you listen, may you find peace and spiritual nourishment in this contemplative time.

If you feel moved to support this ministry’s ongoing work in spreading the beauty of Catholic prayer, please consider a gentle contribution. Your generosity helps sustain these daily reflections and reach more souls seeking quiet prayer.

For those wishing to deepen their daily devotion, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed throughout the day, enriching your spiritual journey with the Psalms and Scripture readings.

May this time of prayer bring you grace and serenity.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-04-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-04-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-03 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to join in a contemplative journey through the Passion of our Lord. Each mystery is presented with reverence and calm, offering a sacred space to reflect on Christ’s love and sacrifice as revealed in the Gospels. This daily prayer is a gentle invitation to deepen your relationship with Jesus through the Rosary, fostering peace and spiritual renewal.

If you find this ministry a blessing, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to provide these prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain this humble offering of faith.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with care and devotion.

May this time of prayer bring you quiet grace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-03-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-03-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-02 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. As we contemplate these sacred events, drawn from the Gospels, we join in a timeless tradition of prayer that nurtures faith and devotion. This gentle reflection offers a moment of peace and spiritual nourishment amid the day’s busyness. We invite you to support this ministry so that we may continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your kindness helps sustain this work of faith and fellowship. For those who appreciate structured daily prayer, consider also listening to our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to offer your support. May this time of prayer bring you closer to the heart of Christ and the joy of His presence.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-02-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-02-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-02-01 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary podcast, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the resurrection, ascension, and heavenly reign of Our Lord Jesus Christ, as well as the joyful hope of the Church. Each mystery is prayed with reverence and quiet reflection, drawing from the rich tradition of the Rosary to nourish your daily prayer life. We encourage you to join us in this sacred time, allowing the mysteries to inspire peace and faith throughout your day. If you find this ministry a blessing, please consider supporting our work to help us continue offering these prayers freely to all who seek them. For those looking to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official prayer throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to support this ministry. May the peace of Christ remain with you always.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-02-01-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-02-01-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-31 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the early life of our Lord and the humble faith of the Blessed Virgin Mary. As we contemplate these sacred moments, we draw closer to the heart of the Gospel and deepen our communion with Christ through the rhythm of the Rosary. We encourage you to consider supporting this ministry, helping to sustain the ongoing offering of daily prayer and spiritual nourishment. For those seeking to enrich their prayer life further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s daily prayers are prayed in the tradition of the Liturgy of the Hours. Visit our website to learn more about supporting this ministry and to access additional resources. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-31-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-31-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-30 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord Jesus Christ. Through this sacred prayer, we reflect on the profound love and mercy revealed in the events of His suffering, drawing strength and grace for our daily lives. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us to continue offering these moments of prayer and contemplation freely to all who seek them. For those desiring to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more. May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual renewal.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-30-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-30-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-29 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting the faithful to contemplate the public ministry of Jesus Christ. Through each mystery, we reflect on the profound moments revealed in the Gospel. This time of prayer offers a serene opportunity to deepen your relationship with Christ and embrace His light in daily life. We warmly encourage you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide these moments of sacred prayer and reflection. For those seeking to enrich their daily spiritual routine, consider also listening to our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official prayers throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to support this ministry. May this prayer bring you peace and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-29-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-29-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-28 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Glorious Mysteries, reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, the coming of the Holy Spirit, the Assumption of Mary, and her Coronation as Queen of Heaven. This sacred prayer invites us to meditate on the triumph of Christ and the hope of eternal life, drawing us closer to the heart of the Gospel as revealed in the Scriptures, including passages from the Gospels and the Acts of the Apostles. We warmly invite you to join in this peaceful moment of prayer and contemplation.

If you find spiritual nourishment in these prayers, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue sharing the Rosary and other Catholic devotions with listeners around the world. Your generosity sustains our mission and allows us to offer these resources freely.

For those seeking to deepen their daily prayer life, we also encourage you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Liturgy of the Hours is prayed in union with the universal Church.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-28-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-28-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-27 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting the faithful to enter more deeply into the Passion of our Lord Jesus Christ. Each mystery is reflected upon with reverence and calm, fostering a spirit of contemplation and union with Christ’s suffering and love. This daily prayer offers a sacred moment to draw closer to the heart of the Gospel as revealed in the Scriptures, particularly in the accounts found in the Gospels.

If you find this ministry a source of grace in your daily prayer life, we gently invite you to support our work so that we may continue to provide these prayers and reflections freely to all who seek them. Your kindness sustains this mission of prayer and devotion.

For those who desire to enrich their daily prayer rhythm further, we also recommend the Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s official prayers throughout the day, complementing the Rosary and deepening your communion with the Church’s liturgical prayer.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual renewal.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-27-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-27-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-26 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the early life of Christ and the grace of His Incarnation. As we gently pray the Hail Marys and contemplate these sacred events, may your heart be drawn closer to the loving presence of Our Lord and Our Lady. This daily prayer offers a moment of calm and spiritual nourishment amid the busyness of life.

If you find this ministry a source of peace and prayerful support, please consider a humble gift to help sustain our work in sharing the Rosary each day. Your generosity allows us to continue offering these prayers freely to all who seek them.

For those who desire to deepen their daily prayer life, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed in a reverent and accessible manner.

May this time of prayer bring you consolation and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-26-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-26-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-25 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary podcast, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join us in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the gift of the Holy Spirit, among other sacred events. As we pray together, we enter into a quiet moment of contemplation, seeking to deepen our communion with Christ and His Church through this traditional Catholic devotion. For those who find nourishment in the daily rhythm of prayer, we also encourage you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed throughout the day. If this ministry supports your spiritual journey, please consider a gentle offering to help sustain and grow this work. Visit our website to learn more. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-25-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-25-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-24 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. Through each decade, we reflect on the Annunciation, the Visitation, the Nativity, the Presentation in the Temple, and the Finding in the Temple, drawing from the Gospel accounts found in Luke and Matthew. This quiet time of prayer offers a sacred opportunity to grow in faith and devotion.

If this ministry blesses your daily prayer life, please consider supporting our work by visiting our website. Your generosity helps us continue offering these prayers freely to all who seek them.

For those looking to enrich their prayer routine further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s daily prayers are prayed in the rhythm of the liturgical hours.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace as you walk with Mary and Jesus today.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-24-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-24-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-23 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the Passion of our Lord through contemplative prayer. Each mystery is thoughtfully presented to guide your reflection on the profound love and sacrifice revealed in the Gospel according to the accounts found in the Gospels of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. This daily prayer offers a peaceful moment to unite your heart with Mary and Jesus in the journey of redemption.

If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting our work with a gift. Your generosity helps us continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Visit our website to learn more about how you can contribute.

For those who desire to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayer is prayed throughout the day, deepening your communion with the liturgical rhythm of the Church.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual refreshment.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-23-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-23-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-22 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, reflecting on the public ministry of Our Lord as revealed through the Gospel. Join us in this sacred time of contemplative prayer, inviting the presence of Christ to deepen your faith and devotion. As you listen, may your heart be drawn closer to the light of the mysteries that illuminate the path of discipleship.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work. Your generosity helps us continue to offer daily prayer and reflection to the wider community.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day in communion with the universal Church.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-22-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-22-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-21 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the coming of the Holy Spirit as revealed in Scripture, including passages from the Gospels and the Acts of the Apostles. This sacred time of prayer offers a moment of calm and spiritual nourishment in the midst of your day. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. For those wishing to deepen their daily prayer life, consider also listening to our Divine Office podcast, which guides the Church’s official prayer throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and offer your support. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-21-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-21-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-20 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and love of Christ through the traditional Rosary. Each mystery is reflected upon with reverence, providing a quiet space for contemplation and spiritual renewal. We encourage you to join us in this sacred prayer, allowing the grace of these mysteries to draw you closer to the heart of Jesus.

If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to offer these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain this humble mission.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with care and devotion.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and deepen your union with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-20-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-20-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-19 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting listeners to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. Each mystery is contemplated with reverence and quiet reflection, fostering a spirit of peace and devotion. As we join together in this sacred prayer, we are reminded of the grace found in daily encounter with God through the Rosary.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our ongoing work in prayer and formation. Your generosity helps us continue to offer these prayers freely to all who seek them.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which leads listeners through the Church’s liturgical hours with Scripture, psalms, and prayers.

May this time of prayer bring you calm and closeness to the Lord.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-19-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-19-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-18 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary podcast, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to join us in reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the gift of the Holy Spirit, as well as the Assumption and Coronation of Mary. Each mystery is presented with reverence and calm, fostering a peaceful environment for contemplative prayer rooted in Scripture from the Gospels and Acts. As you listen, may your heart be drawn closer to the profound joy and hope found in these sacred moments.

If you find spiritual nourishment in these prayers, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue sharing daily Catholic prayer resources. For those seeking to deepen their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which offers the rich tradition of the Liturgy of the Hours.

Thank you for joining us in this sacred time of prayer; may you be blessed with peace and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-18-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-18-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-17 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the Blessed Virgin Mary. Through each mystery, we reflect on the joyful events from the Annunciation to the Presentation in the Temple, drawing closer to the heart of our faith with reverence and quiet contemplation. This prayerful time offers a peaceful moment to unite your intentions with the Church’s daily devotion.

If you find spiritual nourishment in these prayers, please consider supporting this ministry so we may continue to provide these daily reflections freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our mission of prayer and formation.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-17-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-17-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-16 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we pray the Sorrowful Mysteries, reflecting on the profound moments of Christ’s passion and sacrifice. Join us in meditative prayer as we contemplate the Agony in the Garden, the Scourging at the Pillar, the Crowning with Thorns, the Carrying of the Cross, and the Crucifixion. This prayerful time invites a deepening of faith and trust in God’s love and mercy. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping to sustain these daily prayers and spiritual resources. Your generosity enables us to continue offering these moments of quiet reflection and devotion. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, we encourage you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Liturgy of the Hours in a gentle, accessible format. Visit our website to learn more about supporting this ministry and to find additional prayer resources. May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer union with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-16-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-16-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-15 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, reflecting on the public ministry of Our Lord Jesus Christ as revealed in the Gospels of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. Join us in this sacred time of contemplation and devotion, inviting the Holy Spirit to deepen your faith and understanding through each mystery. As you pray along, may your heart be drawn closer to the life and mission of Christ.

If this ministry nourishes your spiritual journey, please consider supporting us so we may continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our work in spreading the beauty of Catholic prayer.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day in communion with the universal Church.

May the peace of Christ be with you as you enter into this time of prayer.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-15-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-15-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-14 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary podcast, we gather in prayer to meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting the faithful to reflect on the Resurrection, Ascension, and other profound moments of Christ’s triumph and the hope of eternal life. This daily offering provides a peaceful space to deepen your devotion and unite your intentions with the Church’s prayerful tradition. We warmly invite you to support this ministry so that we may continue to provide these moments of calm and spiritual nourishment. Your generosity helps sustain the work of sharing daily prayer with souls around the world. For those seeking to enrich their prayer life further, we encourage you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred prayers. May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-14-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-14-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-13 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. Through each decade, we reflect on the profound moments of Christ’s suffering as revealed in the Gospels, drawing close in humble contemplation and trust. This daily prayer offers a serene space to unite your intentions with the heart of Jesus, fostering peace and spiritual renewal.

If you find this ministry a source of grace in your daily prayer life, please consider supporting our work. Your generosity helps us continue to provide these prayers freely to all who seek them. Visit our website to learn more about how you can contribute.

For those wishing to enrich their prayer routine further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s daily prayers are prayed in communion with the universal Church.

May this time of prayer bring you consolation and strength in the Lord’s loving presence.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-13-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-13-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-12 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ through these sacred moments. As we reflect on the Annunciation, Visitation, Nativity, Presentation, and Finding in the Temple, we join our hearts with Mary’s humble and faithful response to God’s plan. This daily prayer offers a gentle rhythm for contemplation and spiritual nourishment.

If this ministry blesses your prayer life, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to provide these daily reflections freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain this humble offering of prayer and devotion.

For those who desire to enrich their daily prayer further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which guides listeners through the Church’s official prayer at morning, midday, evening, and night.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a deeper sense of God’s presence throughout your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-12-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-12-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-11 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Glorious Mysteries, reflecting on the resurrection, ascension, and the coming of the Holy Spirit, as well as the crowning of Our Lady. This prayerful meditation invites a deeper contemplation of the triumph of Christ and the hope it brings to all believers. Rooted in the sacred tradition of the Rosary, this episode offers a calm and reverent space to unite in prayer with the Church.

If you find spiritual nourishment in these daily prayers, please consider supporting this ministry to help sustain and share these moments of grace. Your generosity enables us to continue offering peaceful prayer resources for all who seek them.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, which provides the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours in a gentle and accessible format.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and deepen your communion with Christ and His Blessed Mother.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-11-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-11-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-10 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the loving heart of Our Blessed Mother. As we gently reflect on these sacred moments, we join in contemplative prayer, seeking to grow in faith and grace through the rhythm of the Rosary. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide these daily prayers freely to all who seek spiritual nourishment. For those desiring to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and devotion. Visit our website to learn more and to offer your support. May this time of prayer bring you peace and a deeper sense of God’s presence in your day.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-10-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-10-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-09 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. Through these sacred reflections, we accompany Jesus in His moments of suffering, drawing strength and grace from His example. Each decade is offered with reverence and quiet contemplation, fostering a spirit of peace and devotion.

If this prayerful time has touched your heart, we warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to provide daily opportunities for spiritual growth and connection. Your generosity sustains our mission and allows us to share the beauty of Catholic prayer with many.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day, deepening your communion with the liturgical rhythm of the Church.

May this time of prayer bring you closer to the peace and love of Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-09-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-09-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-08 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting you to reflect on the public ministry of Our Lord as revealed in the Gospel of Matthew, Mark, Luke, and John. Join us in this sacred time of prayer, contemplating the profound moments that illuminate Christ’s mission and presence in the world. As you pray along, may your heart be drawn closer to the mysteries of faith and the loving guidance of Our Blessed Mother.

If you find this ministry a source of spiritual nourishment, please consider supporting our work so we may continue to offer these daily prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain this humble mission.

For those wishing to deepen their daily prayer life, we also invite you to listen to our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers are prayed throughout the day, fostering a rhythm of prayer and praise.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-08-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-08-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-07 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to enter into the joyful contemplation of Christ’s Resurrection, Ascension, the descent of the Holy Spirit, the Assumption of Mary, and her Coronation as Queen of Heaven. Each mystery is reflected upon with reverence, drawing from the Gospel accounts and the sacred tradition to deepen your daily prayer experience. We encourage you to join us in this peaceful moment of devotion, allowing the mysteries to inspire faith and hope in your heart.

If you find this ministry a blessing in your spiritual journey, please consider supporting our work so that we may continue to offer these prayers freely to all who seek them. Your generosity helps sustain our mission of prayer and evangelization.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s Liturgy of the Hours is prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you closer to the peace and grace of our Lord and His Blessed Mother.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-07-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-07-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-06 Rosary - Tuesday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. Through this sacred devotion, we reflect on the profound love and humility revealed in these moments of Christ’s suffering, drawing strength and grace for our daily lives. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us continue to offer these prayers and reflections freely to all who seek spiritual nourishment. For those desiring to expand their daily prayer life, consider also listening to our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s liturgical prayers are prayed throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred rhythms. May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer union with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-06-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-06-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-05 Rosary - Monday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to join in reflecting on the early life of Christ and the grace-filled moments of His earthly journey. Each decade is prayed with reverence, fostering a deeper connection to the mysteries that reveal God’s loving plan. As you listen and pray along, may your heart be drawn closer to the peace and joy found in the Gospel accounts of the Annunciation, Visitation, Nativity, Presentation, and Finding in the Temple (Luke 1; Luke 2).

If this prayerful time enriches your day, please consider supporting this ministry so we can continue to provide these daily prayers freely. Your generosity helps sustain our mission to bring the Rosary and other sacred prayers to listeners worldwide.

For those seeking to deepen their daily prayer life, we also invite you to explore the Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers throughout the day are prayed in a calm and contemplative manner.

May the peace of Christ fill your heart as you journey with us in prayer today.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-05-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-05-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-04 Rosary - Sunday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we pray the Glorious Mysteries, inviting you to meditate on the Resurrection, Ascension, and other profound moments of Christ’s triumph and the hope of eternal life. The prayerful reflection offers a peaceful space to deepen your connection with the Lord through the sacred rhythm of the Rosary. We encourage you to support this ministry prayerfully and financially if you feel moved, helping us continue to provide daily Catholic prayers and reflections. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s liturgical prayers throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and to support this ministry. May this time of prayer bring you calm and grace as you walk with Christ today.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-04-rosary-sunday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SundayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15610409" />
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-04-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-03 Rosary - Saturday - The Joyful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Joyful Mysteries, reflecting on the early life of Our Lord and the profound moments of grace surrounding His birth and childhood. Each mystery invites us to enter more deeply into the humble and joyful events that reveal God’s loving plan. As we meditate on these sacred mysteries, we are gently drawn into a spirit of peace and contemplation.

If this prayerful time nourishes your soul, please consider supporting this ministry to help us continue offering daily prayers and reflections. Your generosity sustains this mission and allows us to share the beauty of the Rosary with others seeking spiritual growth.

For those who wish to enrich their daily prayer life further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers throughout the day are prayed and reflected upon with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you calm and grace as you walk with Our Lady and her Son.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-03-rosary-saturday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/SaturdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15764442" />
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-03-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-02 Rosary - Friday - The Sorrowful Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. As we reflect on these sacred moments, the rosary offers a serene space for contemplation and spiritual renewal. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping to sustain our mission of daily prayer and faith formation. For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the timeless prayers of the Church throughout the day. Visit our website to learn more and join us in these sacred devotions. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-02-rosary-friday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/FridayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15939240" />
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-02-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026-01-01 Rosary - Thursday - The Luminous Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries Daily Rosary, we gather in quiet prayer to meditate on the Luminous Mysteries, inviting the light of Christ’s public ministry to illuminate our hearts. As we reflect on these sacred moments, drawn from the Gospel accounts, we are gently led to deepen our faith and trust in God’s presence. This prayerful time offers a peaceful space to unite our intentions with those of the Church, fostering spiritual growth through contemplative repetition and Scripture references from the Gospels.

If this ministry nourishes your prayer life, please consider supporting us so we can continue to provide daily prayer resources. Your generosity helps sustain this humble offering of faith and devotion.

For those seeking to enrich their daily prayer routine further, we invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, where the Church’s official prayers throughout the liturgical hours are prayed with reverence and care.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and a closer walk with Christ.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2026-01-01-rosary-thursday-the-luminous-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/ThursdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15260016" />
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2026-01-01-luminous-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-12-31 Rosary - Wednesday - The Glorious Mysteries (Daily Catholic Prayer)</title>
      <description>In this episode of St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we gather to pray the Glorious Mysteries, reflecting on the Resurrection, Ascension, and the gift of the Holy Spirit, among other profound moments in the life of Christ and Our Lady. This prayer invites a peaceful meditation on the triumph of grace and the hope found in God’s promises, drawing from the scriptural accounts in the Gospels and the Acts of the Apostles. Join us in this calm and reverent time of prayer as we unite our hearts with the Church’s daily devotion.

If this ministry helps nourish your prayer life, please consider supporting our work. Your generosity enables us to continue providing these daily prayers freely to all who seek to deepen their faith.

For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer rhythm further, we also invite you to explore our Divine Office podcast, offering the Church’s official prayers throughout the day.

May this time of prayer bring you peace and spiritual renewal.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-31-rosary-wednesday-the-glorious-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/WednesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15562485" />
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-31-glorious-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2029-12-30 Daily Rosary - Sorrowful Mysteries</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Sorrowful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the passion and sacrifice of Our Lord. Through each mystery, we reflect on the profound love and mercy revealed in these moments of Christ’s suffering, drawing strength and grace from this sacred devotion. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping us to continue offering these daily prayers freely to all who seek spiritual nourishment. For those wishing to enrich their prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which guides listeners through the Church’s daily liturgical prayers. Thank you for joining us in this peaceful time of contemplation and prayer. May God’s peace be with you always.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-30-rosary-tuesday-the-sorrowful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/TuesdayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15893989" />
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2029-12-30-sorrowful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025-12-29 Daily Rosary - Joyful Mysteries</title>
      <description>In this episode of the St. Helena Ministries – Daily Rosary, we prayerfully meditate on the Joyful Mysteries, inviting you to enter more deeply into the life of Christ and the loving heart of Our Blessed Mother. As we reflect on these sacred events, drawn from the Gospels, we seek to grow in faith and devotion through contemplative prayer. We warmly invite you to support this ministry, helping to sustain these daily moments of spiritual nourishment and community prayer. For those wishing to enrich their daily prayer life further, consider exploring our Divine Office podcast, which offers the Church’s traditional prayers throughout the day. May this time of prayer bring you peace and grace as you journey with us in faith.</description>
      <link>https://sthelenaministries.com/2025-12-29-rosary-monday-the-joyful-mysteries-daily-catholic-prayer</link>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/sthelena-daily-rosary/MondayRosary.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15748482" />
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2025-12-29-joyful-mysteries</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>